好的，我希望您能幸免于最近的两次演讲，并且我假设的主题是
all right I hope you survive the last two lectures and I'm assuming the topics
two lectures and I'm assuming the topics that needed to be covered were covered
那些需要被掩盖的东西被掩盖了，所以我不是你知道我还没有收到
that needed to be covered were covered so I'm not you know I have not received
so I'm not you know I have not received any note contrary to God so we have
任何与上帝背道而驰的音符，所以我们进行了准确的双重演讲，其中有些是
any note contrary to God so we have accuracy dual lectures some of them are
accuracy dual lectures some of them are they may sound a little review but
他们可能听起来有点评论，但希望我们会在
they may sound a little review but hopefully we will do some new things in
hopefully we will do some new things in between and today I want to just go back
从今天开始，我只想回到直接的图形模型，因为
between and today I want to just go back to a directly graphical models because
to a directly graphical models because basically they are the graphical models
基本上，它们是对科学更重要的图形模型
basically they are the graphical models of more importance for scientific
of more importance for scientific applications okay so we need to to cover
应用程序还可以，所以我们需要详细介绍一些内容，提醒您不要
applications okay so we need to to cover a few things in details reminder not
a few things in details reminder not next week next next week all the
下个礼拜下个礼拜
next week next next week all the presentations in the class are going to
presentations in the class are going to start and I'm gonna be randomly picking
开始，我要随机选择名字，我们是说你和你
start and I'm gonna be randomly picking names and we're saying you you and you
names and we're saying you you and you today you you tomorrow
今天，你明天就可以了，所以不要发送给我，
today you you tomorrow okay so don't send me in the quest and
okay so don't send me in the quest and say please can I speak the last can I do
请说，我可以说最后一句话，我可以这样做吗，我可以做到吗，你知道，我认为
say please can I speak the last can I do this can I do that you know and I think
this can I do that you know and I think your presentations it will be useful if
您的演示文稿将非常有用，如果您在实际讲话前一天
your presentations it will be useful if you a day before you actually speak the
you a day before you actually speak the the papers we can make them to be view
我们可以使它们基本上在学期末就可以发表的论文，所以
the papers we can make them to be view basically at the end of the semester so
basically at the end of the semester so that's where you have a few more weeks
那是您还有几周的时间可以写出实际的六页，但是
that's where you have a few more weeks to write the actual six pages okay but
to write the actual six pages okay but there's no point of giving a
没有演讲的必要，然后说，请参阅修改
there's no point of giving a presentation then say please see revise
presentation then say please see revise presentation of course if the
如果演示文稿和论文不同意，当然可以进行演示
presentation of course if the presentation and the paper don't agree
presentation and the paper don't agree in content we're in trouble
在内容上我们有麻烦了，所以基本上不要打扰
in content we're in trouble okay so don't bother basically
okay so don't bother basically submitting them if they are not on the
如果它们不在同一频率上提交，则提交它们
submitting them if they are not on the same on the same frequency
现在下周是科学会议，我不会在这里我有一个主意
now next week is the scientific meeting I am NOT going to be here I have an idea
I am NOT going to be here I have an idea it's avec is going to be here so we may
avec将会在这里，所以如果我参加的话，我们可能会在星期五上课
it's avec is going to be here so we may have a lecture on Friday if I make it on
have a lecture on Friday if I make it on time but for sure I'm not here Tuesday
时间，但是可以肯定的是，我星期二和星期四不在这里
time but for sure I'm not here Tuesday and Thursday okay
所以实际上，这可能是不止一次的演讲，我不会
so actually for this would be most probably more than one lecture I don't
probably more than one lecture I don't know how much we're going to cover today
知道今天我们要支付三场讲座的价格，但是
know how much we're going to cover today the price for three lectures but the
the price for three lectures but the thing I don't have that luxury strong a
我所没有的那种奢侈使这座宫殿最多举办了两次讲座
thing I don't have that luxury strong a maximum of two lectures this palace
maximum of two lectures this palace it's after nineteen from reqtest book
是从reqtest书中读到的19点之后，还从中传授了7个拼写
it's after nineteen from reqtest book and also taught the spelling seven from
and also taught the spelling seven from colors and Friedman PGM book okay so
颜色和Friedman PGM都可以，所以它们都非常出色
colors and Friedman PGM book okay so they're both excellent reached all right
they're both excellent reached all right and as I said for those in who work in
正如我对那些从事科学和工程工作的人说的那样，
and as I said for those in who work in science and engineering this is a very
science and engineering this is a very relevant topic so we may give you
相关主题，以便我们可以为您提供基本的指导，我们将尽力
relevant topic so we may give you basically minders and we'll try to to
basically minders and we'll try to to revisit a few concepts so what you see
重新审视一些概念，因此您在顶部看到的是定向的示例
revisit a few concepts so what you see on the top is an example of a directed
on the top is an example of a directed graph right and on the bottom we see an
右图，在底部，我们看到了该图的无向版本
graph right and on the bottom we see an undirected version of this where you
undirected version of this where you notice we have done what with the
注意我们用流行语做了什么
notice we have done what with the buzzword what it is
buzzword what it is modernization so we have moralized the
现代化，所以我们已经道德化了措辞，例如，七有三
modernization so we have moralized the parlance so for example seven has three
parlance so for example seven has three parents right and you notice four five
父母权利，你会注意到四个五和六个
parents right and you notice four five and six
and six basically we linked them similarly five
基本上我们将它们链接起来类似，五个有两个父母两个和三个，我们
basically we linked them similarly five has two parents two and three and we
has two parents two and three and we made them now we will say that when you
现在使他们成为现实，我们会说，当您动员时，这绝不意味着
made them now we will say that when you mobilize it doesn't by any way imply
mobilize it doesn't by any way imply that whatever conditioning dependence
无论顶部条件图的条件依赖关系如何
that whatever conditioning dependence relationship for the graph on the top
relationship for the graph on the top you are going to have the same relations
您将在底部的图形上具有相同的关系，这可以
you are going to have the same relations on the graph on the bottom and this can
on the graph on the bottom and this can be an issue I mean it's easier to work
是一个问题，我的意思是正确使用此模型更容易，今天，我们
be an issue I mean it's easier to work with this model right and today we're
with this model right and today we're actually going to be talking about
实际上将要谈论无向图，所以有一个
actually going to be talking about undirected graphs okay so there is a
undirected graphs okay so there is a merit to do this but you need to be
这样做是值得的，但是您需要知道，但是这里的条件关系
merit to do this but you need to be aware but the conditional relations here
aware but the conditional relations here they are not the same as the ops on the
它们与底部的操作并不总是一样，所以为什么我们不这样做
they are not the same as the ops on the bottom not always all right so why do we
bottom not always all right so why do we need to understand undirected graphical
需要了解无向的图形模型，这里只是一个例子
need to understand undirected graphical models there is just example
models there is just example think
考虑知识的时间越长
think about the the knowledge the longer
about the the knowledge the longer variables in your graph let's say the
图表中的变量假设图像中没有形成的像素体
variables in your graph let's say the pixel bodies in an image it doesn't make
pixel bodies in an image it doesn't make a sense to actually put directions with
实际为我们指示方向的选举是一种形象的权利
a sense to actually put directions with us the elections being an image right
us the elections being an image right the this pixel effects is the parent of
该像素效果是该像素的父元素，这就是我们的大小
the this pixel effects is the parent of that pixel and that is the size of our
that pixel and that is the size of our picture what does that mean it doesn't
想像一下这意味着什么并不意味着什么，所以我们只是没有
picture what does that mean it doesn't mean anything so we only there's no
mean anything so we only there's no meaning to actually use a direct
实际使用直接图形模型的含义是
meaning to actually use a direct graphical model it's a in the context of
graphical model it's a in the context of famous analysis and more importantly
著名的分析，更重要的是，在如此庞大的分析中使用它无关紧要
famous analysis and more importantly it's not relevant to use it in this huge
it's not relevant to use it in this huge field of special statistics okay you
特殊统计领域好吧，您必须尝试在以下方面对相关性进行建模
field of special statistics okay you have to be try to model correlations in
have to be try to model correlations in a special domain so I'll give you an
一个特殊的领域，所以我给你举一个例子，并基本上说明
a special domain so I'll give you an example and to indicate basically how
example and to indicate basically how different things can be between
有向图模型和无向图模型之间可以有不同的事物
different things can be between directed graphical models and undirected
directed graphical models and undirected graphical model so let's go sit right on
图形化模型，让我们马上就坐吧，这是您可以想到的
graphical model so let's go sit right on no date okay so this is you can think of
no date okay so this is you can think of this as an image and this have the pixel
这作为图像，并且具有正确的像素值，我们认为它们是
this as an image and this have the pixel values right which we take them to be
values right which we take them to be rondo and let's say we put some arrows
回旋曲，让我们说出一些箭头，以确保您获得所有年级的分数
rondo and let's say we put some arrows the way that you secure all this grade
the way that you secure all this grade okay so we look on node X a can you tell
好吧，所以我们看一下节点X a，你能告诉我看一下所有的移植物吗？
okay so we look on node X a can you tell me just looking at this graft all of
me just looking at this graft all of this other knowledge that you see there
您在那边看到的其他知识他们做什么是可以的
this other knowledge that you see there all together what are they what do can
all together what are they what do can we assign them a name in the context of
我们在节点X a和Y的上下文中为它们分配一个名称，因此
we assign them a name in the context of the node X a and Y so it's very
the node X a and Y so it's very carefully all of this knows by the sound
仔细地通过兴奋的声音知道所有这些，当然Mira可以看到
carefully all of this knows by the sound excited except of course Mira can see
excited except of course Mira can see here x2 right it isn't an all together
在这里，x2对x8的上下文不是一个整体
here x2 right it isn't an all together what are they in the context of x8
使毯子好吧，所以市场包括父母包括
the make a blanket okay so the market includes the parents includes the
includes the parents includes the children and what our x12 and explore
孩子们，我们的x12和探索公司行不行
children and what our x12 and explore the corporates okay
the corporates okay obviously is not included right so the
显然不包括在内，所以马尔可夫毯子的想法显然是
obviously is not included right so the idea obviously of the Markov blanket is
idea obviously of the Markov blanket is that we know the values of the Markov
我们知道这个Novak的Markov毯的值是然后提取的
that we know the values of the Markov blanket of this Novak's a then extract
blanket of this Novak's a then extract is conditionally independent of anything
有条件地独立于地面上的其他任何东西，所以很明显，我们
is conditionally independent of anything else in the ground okay so obviously we
else in the ground okay so obviously we have to look very carefully on all this
必须非常仔细地查看所有网格，然后说是的，这就是马尔可夫
have to look very carefully on all this grid here to say yes this is the Markov
grid here to say yes this is the Markov blanket but x2 is not included the x14
毯子，但不包括x2，不包括x14好的，现在让我们看一下
blanket but x2 is not included the x14 is not included okay so let's look now
is not included okay so let's look now the undirected graph the Markov blanket
无向图的马尔可夫毯只是邻居的四个节点
the undirected graph the Markov blanket is only those four nodes the neighbors
is only those four nodes the neighbors because you remember conditional
因为您记得条件独立性基本上是在无方向的情况下
because you remember conditional independence basically in an undirected
independence basically in an undirected graph is defined by the neighbor so if
图是由邻居定义的，因此，如果您描述这些值
graph is defined by the neighbor so if you describe the values of these
you describe the values of these neighbors right x8 is independent
邻居对x8是独立的，因为如果你看这个
neighbors right x8 is independent anything else because if you look this
anything else because if you look this if you think of this operation the graph
如果您想到此操作，则图表将从激发到您拥有的任何其他节点
if you think of this operation the graph from excited to any other node you have
from excited to any other node you have to go through this neighbors this Markov
穿过这个马尔可夫毯子的邻居，如果观察到
to go through this neighbors this Markov blanket and and and if this are observed
blanket and and and if this are observed got blocked okay so point is this
被阻止好了，所以这是在这种情况下的独立性关系
got blocked okay so point is this condition independence relations in the
condition independence relations in the context of undirected graphs are very
无向图的上下文比您看到的要简单得多
context of undirected graphs are very simpler than what you see with a
simpler than what you see with a directed graph so obviously there is a
有向图，所以很明显有一个可以与无向图一起工作的优点
directed graph so obviously there is a merit to actually work with undirected
merit to actually work with undirected graphs so if you want SQ advantages and
图，所以如果您想要SQ的优点和缺点，那么无向图
graphs so if you want SQ advantages and disadvantages so the undirected graphs
disadvantages so the undirected graphs have symmetric you noticed when you look
具有对称性，您在寻找邻居时注意到了
have symmetric you noticed when you look for example for the neighbors is not
for example for the neighbors is not like this is the father
像这样的父亲是没有诺里亚主义的，这是孩子
like this is the father there is norian tation this is the kids
there is norian tation this is the kids we start the comparison you don't have
我们开始比较，您没有像这样的东西
we start the comparison you don't have anything like that
anything like that everything allowed to know the symmetric
一切都允许知道对称的好吧，所以在特殊情况下
everything allowed to know the symmetric alright so in the context of special
alright so in the context of special statistics is very relevant we will say
统计数据非常相关，我们将在今天星期四说，当您
statistics is very relevant we will say it not today on Thursday that when you
it not today on Thursday that when you discuss this cumulative analysis so when
讨论此累积分析，以便当您尝试生成给定X的Y的模型P时
discuss this cumulative analysis so when you try to produce models P of Y given X
you try to produce models P of Y given X and this we will do this in the context
我们将在您知道的条件随机字段的上下文中执行此操作
and this we will do this in the context of conditional random fields you know
of conditional random fields you know the you know undirected graphical models
你知道无向图形模型是非常合适的
the you know undirected graphical models are very appropriate this is very
are very appropriate this is very difficult to do with directly graphical
使用直接图形模型很难实现，但我们在内存方面存在劣势
difficult to do with directly graphical models we have disadvantages in memory
models we have disadvantages in memory we will revisit this today the
今天我们将重新讨论联合概率的私有化
we will revisit this today the privatization of the joint probability
privatization of the joint probability distribution in a direct graphic of
以技巧的方式在Morgan的直接图形中进行分布
distribution in a direct graphic of Morgan's in terms of tricks right
Morgan's in terms of tricks right there's no physical meaning they're not
没有物理意义他们没有赚到您知道的概率，所以您
there's no physical meaning they're not make probabilities you know so you
make probabilities you know so you cannot really interpret things as easy
不能真正像使用定向图形模型那样轻松地解释事物
cannot really interpret things as easy as you do with directed graphical models
as you do with directed graphical models and the parameters that are involved in
而且诊所所涉及的参数很难
and the parameters that are involved in the clinics are very difficult to
the clinics are very difficult to compute so the others are little bit
计算，所以其他的甚至有点复杂，我们可能再次
compute so the others are little bit more complicated even and again we may
more complicated even and again we may see this today or on our first day when
今天或在我们使用直接图形模型的第一天看到这一点
see this today or on our first day when you work with direct graphical models
you work with direct graphical models and naturally local probabilities like
自然地，局部概率（例如参数）不会被提供给观察者
and naturally local probabilities like the parameters are not given spotters
the parameters are not given spotters are normalized this is not the case from
归一化，直接图形模型不是这种情况，因此
are normalized this is not the case from direct graphical models so the
direct graphical models so the normalization requires actually to work
规范化实际上需要使用所有地方的所有点击，并且
normalization requires actually to work with all the clicks everywhere and that
with all the clicks everywhere and that is a very computationally difficult
是一个非常困难的计算问题，实际上大多数
is a very computationally difficult problem ok actually most of the
problem ok actually most of the algorithms have difficulties just
算法的困难仅在于正确地计算
algorithms have difficulties just because of computing properly the
because of computing properly the normalization factor
归一化因子
所以在无向图中，我们基本上唯一的条件关系
because of computing properly the normalization factor
so in an undirected graphs the only conditional relation that we basically
所以在无向图中，我们基本上唯一的条件关系
conditional relation that we basically have played with is what you see here
您在这里看到的是用分隔定义的，所以X a是
have played with is what you see here defined with the separation so X a is
defined with the separation so X a is independent of X B given X C right when
当从xa到xb的任何电源必须使用时，独立于XB的XC权利
independent of X B given X C right when any power from x-a to x-b has to go
any power from x-a to x-b has to go through XC okay and this is what we call
通过XC好吧，这就是我们所说的正常市场产权，因此
through XC okay and this is what we call a normal market property right so for
a normal market property right so for example if you look at nodes 1 &amp; 2 &amp; 6 &amp;
例如，如果您查看节点1＆2＆6＆7
example if you look at nodes 1 &amp; 2 &amp; 6 &amp; 7
7 they're conditionally independent from I
它们有条件地独立于我的意思是1 2＆6 7或加法无关
they're conditionally independent from I mean 1 2 &amp; 6 7 or addition independent
mean 1 2 &amp; 6 7 or addition independent given 3 4 &amp; 5
给定3 4＆5，因为从一或二变为六或
given 3 4 &amp; 5 because to go from one or two to six or
because to go from one or two to six or seven you every part has to grow through
七个，您的每个部分都必须通过3 5＆4成长，这就是全球马尔可夫
seven you every part has to grow through 3 5 &amp; 4 so that's the global Markov
3 5 &amp; 4 so that's the global Markov property the these geometrical property
这些几何特性基本上是根据
property the these geometrical property is basically defined in terms of the
is basically defined in terms of the immediate neighbors of a node so if you
节点的直接邻居，因此，如果修复它们的直接邻居，
immediate neighbors of a node so if you fix their immediate neighbors that's the
fix their immediate neighbors that's the Markov blanket basically this node
马尔可夫毯子基本上使该节点与另一个节点分离
Markov blanket basically this node becomes separated from where the other
becomes separated from where the other nodes okay so this is the local property
节点好，所以这是本地属性，因此您只需查看
nodes okay so this is the local property so you just look at the nodes of of the
so you just look at the nodes of of the neighbors of the node and then there is
节点的邻居，然后就可以了，所以这是一个例子
neighbors of the node and then there is ok so here's one example one is so
ok so here's one example one is so different or three one is independent of
不同或三个独立于另一节点好
different or three one is independent of the other node all right
the other node all right because again 23 are the neighbors of
因为23再一次是有趣的邻居，一旦您阻止了他们，就没有路可走
because again 23 are the neighbors of fun once you block them there is no path
fun once you block them there is no path to go from 1 to any corrupt and and then
从1变到任何腐败，然后您有这个瘫痪的Markov属性
to go from 1 to any corrupt and and then you have this paralyzed Markov property
you have this paralyzed Markov property all right
好吧，如果是的话，如果是的话，你的邻居也这样
all right so if so if yes again your neighbors so
so if so if yes again your neighbors so financial condition independent given
财务状况独立于其他因素（如果没有直接优势）
financial condition independent given the rest if there is not direct edge
the rest if there is not direct edge between them okay
他们之间好记是有条件依赖的
between them okay notes are conditionally dependent given
notes are conditionally dependent given the rest right if there's no s between
其余的，如果它们之间不存在，您能坐下来吗？
the rest right if there's no s between them can you sit up I mean if the amount
them can you sit up I mean if the amount of dissipation is so let's say I'm
耗散是这么说的，我正在看注6 8和X 9以及所有
of dissipation is so let's say I'm looking at the note 6 8 and X 9 and all
looking at the note 6 8 and X 9 and all the other notes of things all right
一切正常的其他注释显然，从X 8 X 9可以找到一条路径
the other notes of things all right obviously there is a path from X 8 X 9
obviously there is a path from X 8 X 9 on this plot all right so the only way
在这个情节上好吧，所以如果有的话，您可以使它独立的唯一方法
on this plot all right so the only way you can make this independent if there
you can make this independent if there is no link and that's why this is called
是没有链接，这就是为什么这被称为成对的markov属性，所以对于
is no link and that's why this is called a pairwise markov property so for
a pairwise markov property so for example is X 7 X 13th independent given
例子是X 7 X 13独立，给定其他所有条件是X 7和X 13
example is X 7 X 13th independent given everything else is X 7 and X 13
everything else is X 7 and X 13 independent given all of the other no
独立于其他所有
是或否是，是的，证据在《谦虚圣经》中的大圣经中给出：
everything else is X 7 and X 13 independent given all of the other no
yes or no yes okay so and the proof is given in the big Bible on Modest by :
是或否是，是的，证据在《谦虚圣经》中的大圣经中给出：
given in the big Bible on Modest by : the serpent is the global properties
蛇是这些成对的全局属性和局部属性
the serpent is the global properties these pairwise and the local property
these pairwise and the local property they're all equivalent so if you start
它们都是等效的，所以如果您从头开始，可以看到其他两个不是
they're all equivalent so if you start on you can saw the other two it's not an
on you can saw the other two it's not an honest theorem and the blue-faced is not
诚实的定理和蓝脸不是很棘手，但我不太了解
honest theorem and the blue-faced is not very tricky but you know not well I
very tricky but you know not well I believe actually talk very well that it
相信实际上讲得很好，从来没有在任何地方正式发表过
believe actually talk very well that it was never formally published anywhere
was never formally published anywhere but is given in the book that you can
但书中给出的内容是，您可以阅读，并且从全国范围开始知道
but is given in the book that you can read you know nationally beginning that
read you know nationally beginning that conditional independence relations
当您记住时，您之间就会知道有条件的独立关系
conditional independence relations between you know when you memorize the
between you know when you memorize the graph basically if you don't maintain
如果您不保持相同条件的独立关系，则基本上是图
graph basically if you don't maintain the same condition independent relations
the same condition independent relations between the director of directed graph
有向图的导演和他们之间的例子之间是有向的
between the director of directed graph and they take example is a directed
and they take example is a directed graph that looks like this okay you
看起来像这样的图，好吧，您还记得这一点，例如
graph that looks like this okay you remember this for example the explaining
remember this for example the explaining away and the undirected version that
离开，看起来像这样的无向版本，所以例如
away and the undirected version that looks like that okay so so for example
looks like that okay so so for example on this graph right with this separation
在这张图上，这种分离描述了从A没有路径
on this graph right with this separation which depicts be there's no path from A
which depicts be there's no path from A to C sorry a and C are independent here
要C对不起a和C在这里是独立的，如果您修复B a和CB来
to C sorry a and C are independent here if you fix B a and C B come
if you fix B a and C B come conditionally independent you remember
有条件地独立，您会记住，所以如果您不处于静止状态
conditionally independent you remember so if you do not be a in still
so if you do not be a in still independent but if you know be alright
独立的，但是如果您知道还可以，请在C语言中完整地解释一下，然后
independent but if you know be alright and in C complete to explain be okay and
and in C complete to explain be okay and that's what the dependence comes so
那就是依赖的来临，所以您马上就可以看到
that's what the dependence comes so immediately you can see that this
immediately you can see that this condition and dependence relations are
条件和依赖关系在有向和有向之间是不一样的
condition and dependence relations are not the same between the directed and
not the same between the directed and sort of the equivalent directed god so
等效的定向神，所以可视化，我将向您展示
sort of the equivalent directed god so visualization and I'm going to show you
visualization and I'm going to show you the maximum organization does not
最大的组织不维持条件独立
the maximum organization does not maintaining the conditional independent
maintaining the conditional independent properties of the directed graph so
有向图的属性，所以让我们简要地看一下这个有向图
properties of the directed graph so let's briefly see this this directed
let's briefly see this this directed graph and the corresponding mobilized
图和相应的动员无向块，因此我们会发蓝
graph and the corresponding mobilized undirected block so will be a blueish we
undirected block so will be a blueish we have given to what is still given 2005
给出了2005仍然给出的结果，好吧，给出两个四个和五个
have given to what is still given 2005 alright given two four and five are
alright given two four and five are conditioned independent right okay so
有条件的独立权利，好吧，让我们看一下这里的两个和五个
conditioned independent right okay so let's look here given to two and five
let's look here given to two and five not conditioned independent was not
没有条件独立不是
因为您实际上可以转到5到6
let's look here given to two and five not conditioned independent was not
because you can actually go to 5 through 6
因为您实际上可以转到5到6
6 remember conditional independence
记住条件独立关系所有有向图都是
remember conditional independence relationships all of directed graphs is
relationships all of directed graphs is is this I call this this what was there
这就是我所说的吗还有更多的实验对吧，您可以
is this I call this this what was there was more experiment right so you can
was more experiment right so you can actually if you were to 5 through 6
实际上，如果您是5到6，那么什么都不会被阻塞，所以克莱尔是
actually if you were to 5 through 6 right nothing is blocked so Claire is
right nothing is blocked so Claire is not independent of heart so we can
不是独立于心脏，所以我们实际上可以解决这个问题并为
not independent of heart so we can actually fix this and make circle for
actually fix this and make circle for this bar to have sort of similar
该条具有类似的条件独立性关系
this bar to have sort of similar conditional independence relationships
conditional independence relationships with an undirected version and the
使用无向版本，答案是肯定的，所以让我们看一下
with an undirected version and the answer is yes so let's look at this
answer is yes so let's look at this example with a little bit more detail
这个例子在这里有更多的细节，所以它说给你两个转弯
example with a little bit more detail here right so it says give you two turns
here right so it says give you two turns out they are not independent
出来，他们不是独立的，好吧，现在在这张图中
out they are not independent okay now is in this diagram that makes
okay now is in this diagram that makes this relation to be destroyed can you
这种关系将被破坏，您可以看得更短些吗？
this relation to be destroyed can you look shorter form tell be working in
look shorter form tell be working in that undirected graph is responsible for
该无向图是导致违反该独立关系的原因
that undirected graph is responsible for violating this independence relation in
violating this independence relation in other ways work between more
其他方式之间的工作更多，但以某种方式导致五不
other ways work between more but somehow resulted on five not being
but somehow resulted on five not being independent of five given for not being
独立于五个给定的，而不是独立于五个给定的哪个链接
independent of five given for not being independent five given to which link is
independent five given to which link is there but creating the problems
在那里但造成问题
七个精氨酸26的裤子，让我们在这种情况下使它们处于这种状态
independent five given to which link is there but creating the problems
the pants of seven arginine 26 there's let's make them in this condition in the
惩罚四个和六个，然后这个有条件的独立关系
penalizing four and six and then this conditional independence relationship
conditional independence relationship that we have on the Left will also be a
我们在左侧也将是一个街区，所以这是您需要做的
that we have on the Left will also be a block so here's what you need to do if
block so here's what you need to do if you want to prove a conditional
你想证明条件独立性，如果你说现在支付和B
you want to prove a conditional independence if you say now pay and B
independence if you say now pay and B given C you only kid so you started off
给定C，你是唯一的孩子，所以你从小马开始就表示一个B和C，
given C you only kid so you started off the pony has denotes a B and C that we
the pony has denotes a B and C that we have okay all right and then you can
没事吧，然后您可以搜索您知道的特殊情况
have okay all right and then you can search on you know particular case
当然，六点和七点不存在，所以实际上不需要知道
certainly six and seven is not there so there's no need to actually you know to
there's no need to actually you know to put six and seven in the picture at all
好吧，在图片中放置六个和七个，所以我们没有六个和七个
put six and seven in the picture at all alright so we don't have any six and
alright so we don't have any six and seven so so if you can see that if you
七个，所以如果您可以看到，如果您对此进行分析，那么这种关系就是
seven so so if you can see that if you analyze this all right this relation is
analyze this all right this relation is actually true it's not the case given to
确实是这样，不是可以对笔进行反抗，所以
actually true it's not the case given to be exploring the pen defied all right so
be exploring the pen defied all right so so again if you restrain yourself on the
再说一次，如果您在这种情况下约束祖先图
so again if you restrain yourself on the ancestral graph alright in this case
ancestral graph alright in this case this beginning of a B and C you can
B和C的开始，您可以保持条件依赖
this beginning of a B and C you can maintain the conditional dependence
maintain the conditional dependence relations from the directed and
来自有向和无向的关系
relations from the directed and undirected
讲座将基本定义，如果
lectures will define basically it won't be an amicable distribution if the
be an amicable distribution if the independence relations implied by the
图暗示的独立性子集的独立性关系
independence relations implied by the graph for subsets of the independent
graph for subsets of the independent elections implied by the distribution
分布所隐含的选举，我们还定义了一个完美的地图，因此
elections implied by the distribution and we also define a perfect map so
and we also define a perfect map so Jason Patric monopoly distribution if I
如果我的J等于P的I，那么Jason Patric的垄断分布
Jason Patric monopoly distribution if I have J equal to I of P the message here
have J equal to I of P the message here is that the directed and undirected
是有向图和无向图是完美的Maps基本上是四个
is that the directed and undirected graphs are perfect Maps basically four
graphs are perfect Maps basically four different sets of distributions okay so
可以使用不同的分布集，所以从这个意义上说，它们功能强大，但
different sets of distributions okay so in this sense they are powerful but
in this sense they are powerful but basically they're pretty mental of each
基本上，他们彼此之间或者我彼此大陆性很强
basically they're pretty mental of each other or I continentally of each other
other or I continentally of each other so let me give you an example I think it
所以让我举一个例子，我认为这是在大选初期，但是我们
so let me give you an example I think it was this was in an early election but we
was this was in an early election but we make an effort to avoid discussion of
尽力避免讨论细节，所以让我们考虑一下
make an effort to avoid discussion of the details so let's consider this
the details so let's consider this undirected graph all right and can you
无向图可以，您能给我一些独立的陈述吗？
undirected graph all right and can you give me some independent statements on
give me some independent statements on this graph simply by looking at this
只需查看此操作即可查看该图
this graph simply by looking at this operation
所以这是独立的，独立条件说给定它们将是什么
so what it is independent the condition independent said given what they'll be
independent said given what they'll be because every math is blocked by DMV and
因为每个数学都被DMV阻止，并且类似地，我们的条件
because every math is blocked by DMV and similarly there'd be our condition
similarly there'd be our condition dependent given agency so the position
依赖给定的代理机构，所以有人可能会问到的职位是很多基本的
dependent given agency so the position that someone may ask is this many basic
that someone may ask is this many basic to go that in quotes exactly the same
用引用完全相同的独立关系表示这一努力
to go that in quotes exactly the same independence relation says this endeavor
independence relation says this endeavor the answer is you can't all right the
答案是你不能很好，答案是“否”，当我在这里演示时
the answer is you can't all right the answer is no and when I demonstrate here
answer is no and when I demonstrate here is two examples you can try as many as
有两个示例，您可以尝试任意多
is two examples you can try as many as you want
you want design this directed graph so this we
设计这个有向图，所以我们可以说a和C是独立的
design this directed graph so this we can say that a and C are independent
can say that a and C are independent given baby that's nice
给婴儿一个很好的你不应该好吧，所以精力
given baby that's nice you should not okay so the energy
you should not okay so the energy independent given B and D which is the
给定的B和D与思想相同，但让我们看一下
independent given B and D which is the same as thought but let's look at the
same as thought but let's look at the northern relation of actually is implied
假设B和D为
northern relation of actually is implied by this graph given a B and D are
by this graph given a B and D are conditionally independent you see that
有条件地独立，您会看到，因此空气是独立的
conditionally independent you see that so it is being independent given air is
so it is being independent given air is being the independent knowing right
是独立的知情权，因为从B到C
being the independent knowing right because there is about to be from B to C
because there is about to be from B to C okay
好吧，工作的事情让我们看看这个
okay so business of work let's look at this
so business of work let's look at this graph we satisfy given baby and you see
图表，我们满足了给定的婴儿，您会看到一个独立的状态，所以这是
graph we satisfy given baby and you see an independent alright so this is the
an independent alright so this is the same relation as there so let's
与那里的关系相同，所以让我们专注于这种独立的关系
same relation as there so let's concentrate on this independent relation
concentrate on this independent relation that say but do you think this
这样说，但您是否认为这与B无关，那是为什么
that say but do you think this independent of B why is that
很明显不是吗
that's obvious isn't it
所以这是独立于我的，我的意思是，没有依赖的东西
so this is independent of me I mean there's no such a thing being dependent
there's no such a thing being dependent of liver okay you can tell other cases
肝好吧，你可以告诉其他情况，你可以说服自己，
of liver okay you can tell other cases right you can convince yourself that
right you can convince yourself that there are a few graphical models
有一些图形模型基本上具有相同的独立性
there are a few graphical models basically have the same independence
basically have the same independence relations and the majority basis
关系和多数依据基本上来自事实
relations and the majority basis basically are coming from the fact of
basically are coming from the fact of this explaining away scenario but we
这可以解释场景，但是我们在课程中已经看到过，所以
this explaining away scenario but we have seen earlier in the course so
have seen earlier in the course so basically what is a conclusion if you
如果将概率的全部子集都包括在内，那么基本上是一个结论
basically what is a conclusion if you take the whole subset of probabilistic
take the whole subset of probabilistic graphical models okay this is the direct
图形模型好吧，这是直接使用它们的图形模型
graphical models okay this is the direct a graphical models right with their
a graphical models right with their condition independence relations to the
与无向图形模型的条件独立性关系
condition independence relations to the undirected graphical models and there is
undirected graphical models and there is a subset of dialectical director that
他们是辩证导演的一个子集
a subset of dialectical director that they're
they're graphical models but basically say the
图形模型，但基本上说相同的条件独立关系
graphical models but basically say the same conditional independence relations
same conditional independence relations models you get the same way Treehugger
你得到的模型与Treehugger一样，所以那里存在关系
models you get the same way Treehugger alright so there is a relation there
alright so there is a relation there that's why the junction tree algorithm
这就是连接树算法成功的原因，所以一半是图形
that's why the junction tree algorithm is successful so the half is a graph
is successful so the half is a graph where if you collapse the matter will
如果您崩溃了，该问题将在哪里看到需要一起单击
where if you collapse the matter will see needs click together
see needs click together megohm elements what you get is you get
兆欧元素您得到的是，您会得到一棵树，除了有
megohm elements what you get is you get a tree okay so apart from that there is
a tree okay so apart from that there is a whole subset basically of conditional
基本上可以得到的条件依赖关系的整个子集
a whole subset basically of conditional dependence relations you can get with
dependence relations you can get with the red gloves but you never get with on
红色的手套，但是你永远都不会戴在左边，所以当我讨论
the red gloves but you never get with on the left so as I discussed about the
the left so as I discussed about the parameterization so the parameterization
参数化，因此我们讨论的参数化必须是实习
parameterization so the parameterization we discuss it has to be internship for
we discuss it has to be internship for potentials defined over the clicks so
在点击次数上定义的电势，因此该电势系统最终确定为
potentials defined over the clicks so this potential system is finalized with
this potential system is finalized with a set of parameters theta C so this is
一组参数theta C，因此单击时有潜力，看到此潜力
a set of parameters theta C so this is potential on click see this potential
potential on click see this potential sculptural basically locally dependence
雕塑之间基本局部依赖
sculptural basically locally dependence between
between but they're not probabilities okay so
但是它们不太可能，所以您不能真正说出最大的工作量
but they're not probabilities okay so you cannot really say maximal working
you cannot really say maximal working alone of this potential
仅凭这种潜力，您基本上就无法进行推断
alone of this potential you cannot basically do inference
you cannot basically do inference because you do inference you will need
因为您进行推断，您将需要将整个Janie分布与
because you do inference you will need to put the whole Janie distribution with
to put the whole Janie distribution with all the potential terms together so the
所有可能的项在一起，所以这实际上是最著名的定理
all the potential terms together so the this is the most famous theorem actually
this is the most famous theorem actually there harmlessly playful theorem that
有无害的嬉戏定理，说所有的联合分布
there harmlessly playful theorem that says that the Joint Distribution of all
says that the Joint Distribution of all this viable swine and undirected graphs
这种有生命力的猪和无向图是可确定的电位的乘积
this viable swine and undirected graphs is the product of potentials definable
is the product of potentials definable maximal cliques divided by an
最大派系除以该分区的组织成本
maximal cliques divided by an organization cost of this partition
organization cost of this partition function taken of the parameters defined
通过单击定义的参数获取的函数，好的组成
function taken of the parameters defined over its click okay this the composition
over its click okay this the composition is not unique and so for example if you
不是唯一的，例如，如果您在这里有潜力
is not unique and so for example if you have potentials here that their
have potentials here that their potentials and you have so carefully
潜力，您非常仔细地注意到这些潜力，您可以
potentials and you have so carefully these potentials which note you can
these potentials which note you can learn them together to power potentials
一起学习它们以发挥潜能，所以这种构成不是唯一的
learn them together to power potentials so this the composition is not unique
so this the composition is not unique as a matter when the algorithms you may
作为算法的问题，您可能希望将其分解为任何
as a matter when the algorithms you may want to make this decomposition as any
want to make this decomposition as any way that the thing is going to simplify
现在事情将简化您的计算类型的方式
way that the thing is going to simplify your type of calculations now the
your type of calculations now the difficult thing here and if I have time
困难的事情在这里，如果我有时间，我们今天将一路与您讨论
difficult thing here and if I have time we will discuss you today all the way
we will discuss you today all the way from Thursday's completing this
从星期四完成此参数theta开始，您会注意到
from Thursday's completing this parameters theta and you notice
parameters theta and you notice unfortunately you will not be able to do
不幸的是，您通常无法在本地产生影响
unfortunately you will not be able to do influence locally in general you would
influence locally in general you would have to this this term here this
在这个术语中必须有这个分区功能
have to this this term here this partition function is that brings
partition function is that brings everything together and is going to
一切都将变得复杂，所以这里是一个例子
everything together and is going to complicate it so here is an example of
complicate it so here is an example of one partition in multiple clicks a clip
多个分区中的一个分区单击一个剪辑1 2 3 2 3 4＆3 5
one partition in multiple clicks a clip 1 2 3 2 3 4 &amp; 3 5 so writers in terms of
1 2 3 2 3 4 &amp; 3 5 so writers in terms of this potential
这种潜力
我提到很多这些与物理学有很大关系，但这
1 2 3 2 3 4 &amp; 3 5 so writers in terms of this potential
I mention a lot of these things are very much related with physics but this
我提到很多这些与物理学有很大关系，但这
much related with physics but this particular statistical physics so this
特殊的统计物理学，所以这种分布是最正常的方式
particular statistical physics so this distribution the most normal way to do
distribution the most normal way to do this is write it in terms of families is
这是写在家庭方面，它与我们真正拥有的高峰有关
this is write it in terms of families is affiliated with its peak we really have
affiliated with its peak we really have seen this before so
以前看过这个，所以这里基本上孩子的潜力是
seen this before so so here basically children potentials is
so here basically children potentials is written to what sport e to the minus C
写入什么运动e到负C处，在那之上定义的能量
written to what sport e to the minus C where is an energy defined over that
where is an energy defined over that particular clickin because the product
特别点击，因为基本上您可以从商品中获得赠品的分配
particular clickin because the product basically you get the gives distribution
basically you get the gives distribution where the energy of the system is the
系统的能量是能量的总和，因此对于最大集团
where the energy of the system is the sum of the energy so for maximal cliques
sum of the energy so for maximal cliques okay so this is the potential defined
好的，所以这是在其信念范围内定义的潜力，现在有了
okay so this is the potential defined over over its belief now this comes with
over over its belief now this comes with different names right as we receive in
当我们在一些书中收到不同的名字时，他们说最大
different names right as we receive in some books they say mister maximum
some books they say mister maximum entropy Tydfil for distribution in
熵Tydfil在机器学习中的分布，他们称之为能量
entropy Tydfil for distribution in machine learning they call this energy
machine learning they call this energy models at the end of the den of the day
在一天的书房尽头的模型，您甚至可以将其视为一头猪
models at the end of the den of the day you can even think of this as a pig
you can even think of this as a pig right well there is no energy or
好吧，没有能量之类的东西，但是你有这些
right well there is no energy or something like that but you have these
something like that but you have these potentials e to the minus exponential
电位e到负指数，因为这样您可以看到自己
potentials e to the minus exponential because that way you can see that you
because that way you can see that you will get a positive product that is
将获得相对于具有因子活塞的正积
will get a positive product that is relative to have the factor piston
relative to have the factor piston distribution right so I think it
分配权，所以我认为如果减去能量，它可能会起作用
distribution right so I think it probably does if the minus energy it
probably does if the minus energy it doesn't have to be motivated by twisting
不必通过扭曲来激发动力，所以这是一个参数化
doesn't have to be motivated by twisting all right so this is a parametrization
all right so this is a parametrization that only accounts for pairwise
只占成对的
当我们说的时候势能很好，但这不是最大的集团，所以我
all right so this is a parametrization that only accounts for pairwise
potentials all right when we say but this is not maximal cliques right so I
当我们说的时候势能很好，但这不是最大的集团，所以我
this is not maximal cliques right so I can see here potential want to 1 3 2 3
可以在这里看到潜在的希望1 3 2 3
can see here potential want to 1 3 2 3 so as I said you can actually do
so as I said you can actually do anything you want here because this
您在这里想要的任何东西，因为这种分解不是唯一的
anything you want here because this factorization is not unique
factorization is not unique so she reviews pairwise potentials okay
所以她可以评估成对的电位，所以她的垃圾箱是一种分析的方式
so she reviews pairwise potentials okay so she the bins are a way of analyzing
so she the bins are a way of analyzing this potentials from their cliques and
他们的势力带来的潜力，这就是所谓的线性模型
this potentials from their cliques and this is what is called a linear model so
this is what is called a linear model so it's potential directed as potential to
它的潜能被定向为潜能，这些潜能被定义为
it's potential directed as potential to be a some basis functions defined over
be a some basis functions defined over the features YC so these are the
YC的特征，所以这些是带有集合的集团产品中的变量
the features YC so these are the variables in the clique product with set
variables in the clique product with set of parameters theta C alright so this is
参数theta C好的，所以这是主要统计数据中的一项崇高权利
of parameters theta C alright so this is a noble right in statistics of the main
a noble right in statistics of the main potential is expressed here selenium or
势在这里表示为硒或
您可能要问自己，未来的功能是否在这里正常运行，所以
a noble right in statistics of the main potential is expressed here selenium or
you may have to ask yourself whether this future functions here P okay so and
您可能要问自己，未来的功能是否在这里正常运行，所以
this future functions here P okay so and sometimes you just fistic aliyou assume
有时候你只是拳头阿里你假设一切都好
sometimes you just fistic aliyou assume something all right
something all right you know the title for mobiles and for
您知道手机的标题，例如您没有的语言模型
you know the title for mobiles and for example language models you don't have
example language models you don't have to learn this future constants well you
很好地学习这个未来的常数，你可以知道你可以设想投掷
to learn this future constants well you can you know you can envision throwing
can you know you can envision throwing and lots of this function so letting the
还有很多此功能，因此让数据找出需要哪些功能
and lots of this function so letting the data figure out which ones are needed
data figure out which ones are needed and the second problem would be to
第二个问题是计算这些参数theta C和
and the second problem would be to calculate those parameters theta C and
calculate those parameters theta C and we will say that's where the concept of
我们要说的是随机优化的概念
we will say that's where the concept of stochastic optimization will come in in
stochastic optimization will come in in in the various parameters are computed
计算各种参数中的值，以便最大派系上的所有势能
in the various parameters are computed so potential over the maximal clique all
so potential over the maximal clique all right so the potential is to this linear
对，所以潜力就是这个线性项这里的分布
right so the potential is to this linear term here the distribution so this
term here the distribution so this distribution is the product of all the
分布是所有潜力的产物，因此
distribution is the product of all the potentials so the
potentials so the information of all of his limbs so I'm
所有他四肢的信息，所以我要对所有
information of all of his limbs so I'm going to have the summation of all of
going to have the summation of all of this it's a function of times theta C
这是theta C下降导致点击率下降的函数-
this it's a function of times theta C decline over leads click - the
decline over leads click - the normalization factor Z of people ok and
正常人的归一化因子Z可以再次看到，如果
normalization factor Z of people ok and again you see that this animal kills if
again you see that this animal kills if theta is going to be coming in all the
theta将会一直存在，如果他们
theta is going to be coming in all the time and it's going to be a should they
time and it's going to be a should they because it's not like okay this is
因为这不好，它与Y成正比，所以我们不需要
because it's not like okay this is proportional to Y we don't need to this
proportional to Y we don't need to this so unfortunately if you're going to
所以不幸的是，如果您要估计这些参数的响应
so unfortunately if you're going to estimate these parameters respond that
estimate these parameters respond that those are powerful through this
通过这个归一化术语，这些功能很强大，例如
those are powerful through this normalization term okay so for example
normalization term okay so for example when we try to delete a maximum
当我们尝试删除最大似然估计或地图估计时
when we try to delete a maximum likelihood estimation or map estimation
likelihood estimation or map estimation where you can envision if you like this
您可以在此处设想是否可以尝试最大化此权利，以及
where you can envision if you like this can try to maximize this right and if
can try to maximize this right and if you do MLA this term is going to be
你做MLA这个术语将很难计算，因为你会
you do MLA this term is going to be difficult to compute because you will
difficult to compute because you will require integration basically on YC or
要求基本上在YC或潜力的乘积上进行集成，以便
require integration basically on YC or the product of the potential so that
the product of the potential so that would be very difficult time to operate
很好的时间将非常困难，因此这是一个例子
would be very difficult time to operate all right so it was an example if this
all right so it was an example if this future functions are if so we paralyze
如果未来的功能是这样的话，我们会让我忘了提及的领域瘫痪市场
future functions are if so we paralyze market on the field I forgot to mention
market on the field I forgot to mention that the field is basically the
基本上，这个领域是替代世界
that the field is basically the alternative world that goes for this
alternative world that goes for this undirected graphical models so we only
无方向性的图形模型，所以我们只认为它们使潜力瘫痪了，我们
undirected graphical models so we only think they paralyze potentials and we
think they paralyze potentials and we assume that each of the body which can
假设每个可以取K值的身体，那么这个未来
assume that each of the body which can take K values and so this future
take K values and so this future functions are basically indicator
功能基本上是指示器功能，因此在这种情况下，
functions are basically indicator function so in this case this particular
function so in this case this particular indicator function takes the value 1
当变量Y else是day并且变量
indicator function takes the value 1 when the variable Y else is day and the
when the variable Y else is day and the value of YT is equal to K ok so and so
YT的值等于K ok，所以您可以有效地想到这一点
value of YT is equal to K ok so and so effectively you can think of this you
effectively you can think of this you know F is a vector of length K squared
知道F是一个长度为K平方的向量，因为您有K乘以K个变量
know F is a vector of length K squared because you have K times K variables
because you have K times K variables okay so the petition basically can be
好吧，请愿书基本上可以写成一张桌子，因为如果您尝试
okay so the petition basically can be written as a table because if you try to
written as a table because if you try to calculate the potential for values of y
计算y es和YT等于a和Kelly的值的可能性
calculate the potential for values of y es and YT equals a and Kelly so
es and YT equals a and Kelly so effectively what you need to do is you
实际上，您需要做的是，您可以看到这是
effectively what you need to do is you can see that this is the exponential of
can see that this is the exponential of the JK parameter theta s T okay so in
JK参数theta可以，因此从某种意义上说
the JK parameter theta s T okay so in some sense there is a similarity between
some sense there is a similarity between for this discrete model using tables and
对于使用表并使用此功能的离散模型，例如
for this discrete model using tables and using this function okay so for example
using this function okay so for example based you know can be any indicator
根据您所知，可以是几分钟内的任何指标功能
based you know can be any indicator function of a few minutes
function of a few minutes these are indexed in the text okay
这些通常会在对应的文本中索引
these are indexed in the text okay typically of the corresponding
typically of the corresponding parameters all right so this function is
参数好，所以这个函数是一个二进制函数，可以取值0
parameters all right so this function is a binary function can take the value 0
a binary function can take the value 0 over 1 so this way you can identify
超过1，这样您就可以识别某些单词，例如
over 1 so this way you can identify certain words so if you have for example
certain words so if you have for example this is for triplet so if you have a
这是三胞胎，所以如果你有一个我和G的世界，或者你知道什么
this is for triplet so if you have a world I and G or you know or something
world I and G or you know or something similar where the problem is if you try
类似的问题出在哪里，如果您尝试这样做是为了获得真实的文本，而您
similar where the problem is if you try to do this for a real text right and you
to do this for a real text right and you take you know 26 letters in the alphabet
让您知道字母表中有26个字母，因此基本上会得到26:58
take you know 26 letters in the alphabet so this will result basically to 26:58
so this will result basically to 26:58 parameters theta so will be
参数θ，因此在计算上将是一件非常困难的事情
parameters theta so will be computationally a very difficult thing
computationally a very difficult thing to do alright so it's not like you're
做得很好，所以这就像您要填充数以百万计的表一样
to do alright so it's not like you're going to populate tables with millions
going to populate tables with millions of parameters and you're going to do
参数，您将对计算机执行某种MLE，因此这不会
of parameters and you're going to do sort of MLE to computer so this will not
sort of MLE to computer so this will not work very well
工作很好很好，所以现在我回到了
work very well okay so now I went to the back to and
okay so now I went to the back to and slowly to the Ising model and revisited
慢慢地回到伊辛模型，然后基本上重新审视了一些想法
slowly to the Ising model and revisited basically some of the ideas with this
basically some of the ideas with this person and see how we can train this
人员，看看我们如何训练hostak优化的模型
person and see how we can train this model which the hostak optimization the
model which the hostak optimization the Ising model we're looking on a good in
我们正在寻找的二维模型是伊辛模型
Ising model we're looking on a good in two dimensions or three dimensions we're
two dimensions or three dimensions we're basically trying to mimic the behavior
基本上是试图模仿磁铁的行为，所以这些二元动物
basically trying to mimic the behavior of magnets so these animals of binary
of magnets so these animals of binary variables plus minus one you can think
变量加减一，您可以想到这种向上旋转向下旋转的类型
variables plus minus one you can think of this spin up spin down type of things
of this spin up spin down type of things when neighboring spins particularly in
当邻居旋转时，特别是向同一方向旋转时，您会得到所谓的
when neighboring spins particularly in the same direction you get what's called
the same direction you get what's called ferromagnets when they try to align in
当铁磁体试图沿相反方向对齐时，您会得到
ferromagnets when they try to align in opposite direction you get
opposite direction you get antiferromagnets sometimes you get to be
反铁磁体有时您会表现出这种行为方式
antiferromagnets sometimes you get to be behaving this way how to behave that way
behaving this way how to behave that way and then in some sense you have a phase
然后从某种意义上讲您有一个相变好吧，您可能会认为这是一个
and then in some sense you have a phase transition okay you may think this is a
transition okay you may think this is a toy problem it's a very biblical problem
玩具问题，这是一个非常圣经的问题，我发布了一些参考资料
toy problem it's a very biblical problem and some of the references of I posted
and some of the references of I posted actually not surprising they're like
其实这并不奇怪，因为过去五年来，就像
actually not surprising they're like from the last five years okay because if
from the last five years okay because if you can do this problem properly with
您可以使用许多中的数百万个应用程序正确地解决此问题
you can do this problem properly with millions of applications in in in many
millions of applications in in in many different areas and of course you must
不同的区域，当然，您必须相似，好吧，所以位置
different areas and of course you must similarity hello okay so the position
similarity hello okay so the position from the model so the potential is not
来自模型，所以潜力不是这样，所以我们在这里看
from the model so the potential is not like this so we're looking here at the
like this so we're looking here at the pairwise potential obviously each of
成对势显然，这些变量中的每一个都可以旋转或旋转
pairwise potential obviously each of these variables can be spin up or spin
these variables can be spin up or spin down so plus minus one all right so it's
向下，所以再加上一个减一，所以它在我们的桌子上，我们将这些值中的每个
down so plus minus one all right so it's on our table each of those values we're
on our table each of those values we're gonna write it as a to W and E minus W
要将其写为W和E减去W，而W基本上使用相同的值
gonna write it as a to W and E minus W who use the same value basically to
who use the same value basically to describe what this probabilities and the
描述这种可能性和故事将要发生的情况
describe what this probabilities and the story is going to be on
story is going to be on - somehow we we have to computer or
-我们必须以某种方式计算机或询问您是否记得独立性
- somehow we we have to computer or askew you remember the independence of
askew you remember the independence of the energies that we used before right
我们之前使用的能量来自
the energies that we used before right what's the local energy here from the
what's the local energy here from the system
系统记住，您必须学习
system remember you have to learn with the
remember you have to learn with the potentials to be at work for I mean the
电位在起作用，因为我的意思是这根电缆通往能量的电位
potentials to be at work for I mean the potential in this cable to the energy
potential in this cable to the energy here okay no energy means high
在这里好吧，没有能量意味着高概率，所以你能告诉我
here okay no energy means high probability so so can you tell me from
probability so so can you tell me from all of this looking at the stable which
所有这一切都看在稳定的情况下，那会给你低
all of this looking at the stable which situation will give you that the low
situation will give you that the low energy so that the W is positive and
能量使W为正并确定阿拉伯人为负W因此伽马
energy so that the W is positive and determine the Arabs is minus W so gamma
determine the Arabs is minus W so gamma is positive which configurations are
肯定的是，如果伽玛为
is positive which configurations are going to give you low energy if gamma is
going to give you low energy if gamma is positive
积极的
记住，这是配置1加1这是4减1这是加
going to give you low energy if gamma is positive
remember this is the configuration one plus 1 this is 4 minus 1 this is plus
记住，这是配置1加1这是4减1这是加
plus 1 this is 4 minus 1 this is plus minus 1 plus minus 1 so which
减1减-1，这样可以为您提供哪些配置
minus 1 plus minus 1 so which configurations will give you will give
configurations will give you will give you the longest tendency of the highest
如果能量为负W，则您具有最高概率的最长趋势
you the longest tendency of the highest probability if the energy is minus W
记住意味着负一百就是-50或零或10
remember means minus a hundred is whatever - a 50 or zero or 10
whatever - a 50 or zero or 10 so which configurations are going to be
因此在两种情况下哪种配置都将通过它
so which configurations are going to be over it in both case which means either
over it in both case which means either the left or on speed up or they're both
左或加速，或者它们都下降，所以基本上是系统
the left or on speed up or they're both down spin down so basically the system
down spin down so basically the system will try to give you the same
会尝试在整个过程中为您提供相同的旋转安排
will try to give you the same arrangements of the spins throughout the
arrangements of the spins throughout the lattice ok and and of course you get the
晶格确定，并且当W为负时，您当然会得到相反的效果
lattice ok and and of course you get the opposite effect when the W is negative
opposite effect when the W is negative okay so in in the trivial sense if you
好吧，从某种意义上来说，如果您想让WS保持不变就可以了
okay so in in the trivial sense if you want if you make WS stay constant okay
want if you make WS stay constant okay you can get sort of a simple the most
您可以得到这个伊辛12号最简单，最明显的版本
you can get sort of a simple the most obvious version of 12 of this Ising
obvious version of 12 of this Ising model
好的模型，所以我们讨论所有这些
model alright so we discuss all of this
alright so we discuss all of this because I mentioned that the
因为我提到了对此的归一化常数
because I mentioned that the normalization constant for this you know
normalization constant for this you know market on the princes is there today
王子的市场今天就在那里，所以一般来说要计算归一化
market on the princes is there today so in general to compute a normalization
so in general to compute a normalization term living from the Ising model is
Ising模型中的长期生存是np-hard
term living from the Ising model is np-hard
np-hard ok and actually
好的，实际上你知道我在看这个
ok and actually you know I was looking at it this
you know I was looking at it this morning you can look at if you pay a
早上你可以看看你是否在远处，我是
morning you can look at if you pay a distance I am yes
distance I am yes you know 10 15 years ago that basically
你知道10年前15基本上给了苹果，而且苹果有多困难
you know 10 15 years ago that basically gives Apple and how difficult is the
gives Apple and how difficult is the computer normalization in a simple
在简单的二维Ising模型中进行计算机归一化，所以现在
computer normalization in a simple two-dimensional Ising model okay so now
two-dimensional Ising model okay so now I see one that is five by five you can
我看到有一个五乘五的人，您可以手动做10乘十的人，您可以
I see one that is five by five you can do it by hand 10 by 10 you can do it by
do it by hand 10 by 10 you can do it by can try to do it in a million by Amelia
可以尝试由Amelia用一百万美元做到
can try to do it in a million by Amelia but okay that's a very difficult
but okay that's a very difficult complicated things there is a relation
复杂的事情在伊辛模型和亚洲人之间有关系
complicated things there is a relation between the Ising model and the asian
between the Ising model and the asian graphical models we actually if you may
图形化模型，实际上，如果您愿意的话，那么某种程度上
graphical models we actually if you may be for that but somehow some of the
be for that but somehow some of the examples we we use this ideas so if I'd
例子中，我们使用了这种想法，因此，如果我使Ising模型瘫痪了
examples we we use this ideas so if I'd taken the Ising model paralyzed
taken the Ising model paralyzed potentials alright so I can write this
潜力不错，所以我可以这样写，所以我的行
potentials alright so I can write this as this alright so the line of my
as this alright so the line of my distribution is minus the summation of
分布减去这些项的总和请记住，因为我们有
distribution is minus the summation of this terms remember because we had the
this terms remember because we had the original - lab menu I still have the
原始-实验室菜单我仍然有相同的事情，因为此Y值必须
original - lab menu I still have the same thing because this Y value must
same thing because this Y value must replace minus 1 okay all right so
替换为负1好吧，所以基本上这就像卖一个
replace minus 1 okay all right so basically this is like selling one of
basically this is like selling one of the energies on this time somewhere over
这一次的能量在双绞线上方的某个地方，如果你想写这个
the energies on this time somewhere over the pair's and if you want to write this
the pair's and if you want to write this in a matrix form
以矩阵形式好吧，你会穿上一半，所以当
in a matrix form alright you will put on a half so when
alright you will put on a half so when because this is another directed graph
因为这是另一个有向图，您不会考虑
because this is another directed graph you don't account the interactions that
you don't account the interactions that say from outside and say twice okay so
从外面说两次，好吧，所以也许你可以看到这看起来
say from outside and say twice okay so so maybe you can see that this looks
so maybe you can see that this looks like a Gaussian Marco I mean those in
像高斯马可（Gaussian Marco），我的意思是图形模型中的人
like a Gaussian Marco I mean those in graphical model alright
graphical model alright but obviously you will need something to
但显然，您将需要一些东西来模仿最小项和您的操作方式
but obviously you will need something to mimic the minterm and the way you do
mimic the minterm and the way you do this is by introducing an external field
这是通过在能量函数中引入一个看起来像
this is by introducing an external field in the energy function that looks like
in the energy function that looks like this okay
好的，如果您在此，您可以进行身体思考
this okay you can think physically if you in this
you can think physically if you in this magnet model right you want to control
您想要控制系统明显磁化的磁铁模型
magnet model right you want to control the obvious magnetization of the system
the obvious magnetization of the system okay if this is a composition of a
好的，如果这是物质系统和al-ahli的组合
okay if this is a composition of a material system and al-ahli
material system and al-ahli you can control maybe the average
您可以控制大概的平均成分
you can control maybe the average composition you know
composition you know this can be related to an external
这可能与外部磁场或类似的东西有关
this can be related to an external magnetic field or something like that so
magnetic field or something like that so in the context of what we do is we
在我们所做的事情中，我们基本上以此来增强能量
in the context of what we do is we basically enhance the energy with this
basically enhance the energy with this term beta transpose Y and immediately
术语Beta转置Y，您可以立即保存以将它们塞在一起，然后
term beta transpose Y and immediately you can save to plug things together and
you can save to plug things together and you complete the square
你完成广场，基本上你可以告诉我们你
you complete the square you basically you can tell us this you
you basically you can tell us this you know it's in mobile as a graphical
知道它作为图形浏览器图形模型在移动设备中
know it's in mobile as a graphical browser graphical model
browser graphical model all right the relation between variables
好吧，变量之间的关系基本上是直接的，所以精度
all right the relation between variables is basically direct so the precision for
is basically direct so the precision for the Gaussian model is basically the
高斯模型基本上就是您所了解的这些链接的优势
the Gaussian model is basically the strength of these links that you know in
高斯职位实际上很容易，因为提名高斯
a Gaussian position actually is very easy because the nomination for Gaussian
easy because the nomination for Gaussian is is the determinant of 2 Pi Sigma then
是2 Pi Sigma的决定因素，那么您可以在尺寸中使用
is is the determinant of 2 Pi Sigma then you can do this in the dimensions with a
you can do this in the dimensions with a cost that goes to they came when I'm
当我一直处于沉浸式模式时，他们付出的代价是正确的
cost that goes to they came when I'm constantly in immersive mode the right
constantly in immersive mode the right if you have de the pixels and insulin
如果您有像素并且胰岛素可以是负1，我们将不得不听起来
if you have de the pixels and insulin can be as minus 1 we will have to sound
can be as minus 1 we will have to sound to find an organization over to the
寻找一个掌权的组织
to find an organization over to the power
你知道其中之一-好的，这就是我提到的这是np-hard的地方
you know one of those - okay and this is where I mentioned that this is np-hard
where I mentioned that this is np-hard okay so those initial to normalize the
好的，所以那些最初对Ising模型进行归一化的人不是很容易归一化
okay so those initial to normalize the Ising model not very easy to normalize
Ising model not very easy to normalize very much
当然，而且在很多方面，您将
very much and of course in many ways you will
and of course in many ways you will think of the Ising model being trivial
认为伊辛模型是微不足道的，但高斯模型要丰富得多
think of the Ising model being trivial but the Gaussian is much more rich model
but the Gaussian is much more rich model but we can see there is a complexity
但我们可以看到信号中存在复杂性，您可以一概而论
but we can see there is a complexity there in a signal you can generalize
there in a signal you can generalize actually if you have a fully connected
实际上，如果您拥有完全连接的Ising模型，那么所有条目
actually if you have a fully connected Ising model all right so all the entries
Ising model all right so all the entries in the W no despair potentials but you
在W中没有绝望的潜力，但您拥有W获得的所有答案
in the W no despair potentials but you have all the answers W you get with the
have all the answers W you get with the squirrel have to network and I think
松鼠必须联网，我认为这是
squirrel have to network and I think this was one of the many applications of
this was one of the many applications of probabilistic graphical models back in
概率图形模型可以追溯到七十年代或八十年代
probabilistic graphical models back in the seventies or eighties all right and
the seventies or eighties all right and the I'm gonna give you only an example
我只给你一个网络业务的例子
the I'm gonna give you only an example of web business so in this little
of web business so in this little networks basically with this you provide
基本上，您可以利用网络来提供其余时间的图像，
networks basically with this you provide the rest of time in images all right and
the rest of time in images all right and system system was missing and I said
系统系统不见了，我说他叫什么名字，你知道那是谁
system system was missing and I said what is his name you know who is that
what is his name you know who is that person right because my bank cannot take
是对的，因为我的银行无法提取所有像素并进行处理，因此
person right because my bank cannot take all the pixels and process them so the
all the pixels and process them so the idea here is to give this training
这里的想法是给这个训练图像缺少很多黑色像素
idea here is to give this training images with lots of black pixels missing
images with lots of black pixels missing all right and then this social network
好的，然后这个社交网络试图弄清楚它的作用
all right and then this social network is trying to figure out to what it
is trying to figure out to what it corresponds and you can see this of the
对应，您可以在一些互动中看到恢复映像
corresponds and you can see this of the recovery images in some interactive
recovery images in some interactive kostik optimization so per version of
kostik优化，因此，根据该算法的每个版本，我们将重新介绍
kostik optimization so per version of this algorithms and we will revisit we
this algorithms and we will revisit we will visit in today or on Thursday this
将会在今天或星期四访问此算法，所以
will visit in today or on Thursday this algorithm okay so
所以这是这种成像中的归因问题，那就是
so this is sort of the imputation problem in in this imaging and that's
problem in in this imaging and that's why it's called associative memory is
为什么将其称为联想记忆，就像您知道自己记忆的东西一样
why it's called associative memory is like you know you have memorize things
like you know you have memorize things but you know you want to be able to make
但您知道您希望能够使用不完整版本的
but you know you want to be able to make decisions using incomplete version of
decisions using incomplete version of this images and figure out what they are
这张图片，弄清楚它们没什么，这实际上给了你很多
this images and figure out what they are okay this actually give you a lot of
okay this actually give you a lot of details of this because we will do
这方面的细节，因为我们将使用渐变方法来解决这些问题
details of this because we will do gradient methods to address these
gradient methods to address these problems the method that in I indicated
我在这里专门指出他们的信息的方法存在问题
problems the method that in I indicated here their information specifically
这是一个加一，然后必须是这样的加一，所以在某种意义上
this is plus one then has to be plus one something like that so in some sense
something like that so in some sense this is what this does
这是可以的，所以有一个解析解决方案
this is what this does okay so there is an analytical solution
okay so there is an analytical solution to that problem of course this have to
对于这个问题，当然必须权衡
to that problem of course this have to be weighted with the strength of the
be weighted with the strength of the interactions of the pixel s with the
像素s与其他像素的相互作用
interactions of the pixel s with the other pixel thing okay there is a
other pixel thing okay there is a mathematical solution as I said but that
我说过的数学解决方案，但我们将与梯度讨论
mathematical solution as I said but that we will discuss with the gradient
we will discuss with the gradient methods this also goes you know it's
您也知道这与所谓的“我们”非常相关的方法
methods this also goes you know it's very much related to what's called we
very much related to what's called we can you
你能行吗，因为妈妈的罪过基本上是
can you it works as mama sins are basically
it works as mama sins are basically extensions of this hostile models where
这种敌对模型的扩展，您只需在其中介绍他和动物
extensions of this hostile models where you simply introduce him and animals in
you simply introduce him and animals in addition to what we saw up to now okay
除了我们到目前为止所看到的，还好，所以我要说的更多，
addition to what we saw up to now okay so I'm going to say much more and
so I'm going to say much more and alright so and limit pennies on this
好吧，就此限制便士
在六个月中非常受欢迎的另一个名字是Bobby Luanne
so I'm going to say much more and alright so and limit pennies on this
another name that is very popular in in six and it's that's Bobby Luanne a it's
在六个月中非常受欢迎的另一个名字是Bobby Luanne
six and it's that's Bobby Luanne a it's like the Ising model but here you are
像Ising模型一样，但是在这里您正在寻找多个离散状态
like the Ising model but here you are looking for multiple discrete states
looking for multiple discrete states so I increased three discrete states and
所以我基本上增加了三个离散状态和相同强度的键
so I increased three discrete states and the same strength of the bonds basically
the same strength of the bonds basically say the table form of these potentials
说这些潜力的表格形式看起来像这样，如果我可以回头
say the table form of these potentials looks like this okay I can turn back if
looks like this okay I can turn back if you ask me I can recognize different
您问我，我可以认识到使用
you ask me I can recognize different problems that I came across using the
problems that I came across using the first model when I was a graduate
当我还是研究生时的第一个模型，所以这是非常重要的
first model when I was a graduate student so this is a very important
student so this is a very important model in multiple areas okay so I'm
可以在多个区域进行建模，所以我可以肯定，如果您出售一些好的零件
model in multiple areas okay so I'm certain if you sell some good parts
certain if you sell some good parts model you will come with a million
模型，您将拥有一百万，基本上可以点击，因为有一个
model you will come with a million basically hits okay because there's a
basically hits okay because there's a lots of crazy ones so to me Sam
很多疯子，所以对我来说山姆
所以基本上是Pat模型的托​​管应用，我想您
basically hits okay because there's a lots of crazy ones so to me Sam
so an application of the hosting of the Pat's model basically and I think you
所以基本上是Pat模型的托​​管应用，我想您
Pat's model basically and I think you guys worked on a homework on this kind
伙计们从事这项功课，超越了所有人的摇摇欲坠
guys worked on a homework on this kind of beyond the shakiest strength all
of beyond the shakiest strength all right and trying to find this very
正确，并试图找到这个非常大的山估计或最低的能量
right and trying to find this very mountain estimate or the lowest energy
mountain estimate or the lowest energy of the system and you notice when J is
的系统，并且您注意到如果得到群集但J很大，则J很大时
of the system and you notice when J is very big if you get clusters but they're
very big if you get clusters but they're spin up when J is very low you have very
如果J很低，则旋转起来，实际上，如果您想要
spin up when J is very low you have very small clusters actually if you want to
small clusters actually if you want to you know
你知道现在记得主要的应用程序之一
you know now remember one of the main application
now remember one of the main application supports models if you want to get
如果您想获得晶体微观结构的样本，则可以支持模型
supports models if you want to get samples of crystal micro structures this
samples of crystal micro structures this is how you do it
就是您如何做到的，所以这些事情基本上可以在
is how you do it alright so those things can basically in
alright so those things can basically in nice particles but you can figure out
不错的粒子，但您可以弄清楚您怎么说这是一个说法
nice particles but you can figure out how you say here's one claim there's
how you say here's one claim there's another grain and another grain stuff
另一种谷物和另一种谷物的东西，这可以模仿
another grain and another grain stuff this is something that can mimic a
this is something that can mimic a nucleation processing and will give you
成核处理，如果我们要再次得到它，它将给您
nucleation processing and will give you if you're going to get it again if we
if you're going to get it again if we give you definitions of a pretty crystal
给你一个漂亮的晶体微观结构的定义
give you definitions of a pretty crystal microstructure okay some point between
microstructure okay some point between for jelly you have a phase transition
对于果冻，您具有相变权，这是非常重要的领域
for jelly you have a phase transition right and this is a very important area
right and this is a very important area of research trying to compute actually
尝试实际计算相变发生时间的研究人员
of research trying to compute actually when the phase transition takes place
when the phase transition takes place not an easy problem maybe some colors
这不是一个容易的问题，也许有些颜色，因为它支持更多的灯光
not an easy problem maybe some colors because this supports more the lights
because this supports more the lights were there they density of the color
在那里，它们的颜色密度保持了您所处的状态，所以您不会
were there they density of the color stays what state you are so you don't
stays what state you are so you don't just black and white but different
只是黑白，但颜色不同我想如果您点击一下
just black and white but different colors I think if you click this little
colors I think if you click this little library from Kevin left this to looks
凯文（Kevin）图书馆将其留给您看，您将看到对应的K是多少
library from Kevin left this to looks you will see what's the corresponding K
you will see what's the corresponding K for this discussing some sort of
为此，我们讨论了该模型的某种复杂性，因此这里
for this discussing some sort of complexity of this model so here the
complexity of this model so here the actual pixel values is this actually
实际的像素值就是我在这里所拥有的
actual pixel values is this actually what I have in here
what I have in here all right this particles okay and they
好的，这个粒子还可以，它们是围绕网格定义的，因此
all right this particles okay and they are defined about a grid so a mid way to
are defined about a grid so a mid way to more than just Y variables is an
不仅仅是Y变量是一个不活跃的模块，但是我应该
more than just Y variables is an underactive module okay but I should
underactive module okay but I should observe variations of this nodes and a
观察此节点的变化，并以一种很好的方式描述
observe variations of this nodes and a very good way to describe the
very good way to describe the subservience is to redirect it model so
subservience是重定向它的模型，所以实际上您拥有的是
subservience is to redirect it model so really what you have is you have a
really what you have is you have a mixture and on the Left model to
混合和在Left模型上基本上描述了a上的相关性
mixture and on the Left model to describe basically the correlations on a
describe basically the correlations on a grid of the Y variables and then to
Y变量的网格，然后描述观察结果，
grid of the Y variables and then to describe the observations you have a
describe the observations you have a direct okay
直接好吧，如果您打算隐藏巨人
direct okay so if you plan to hide the giant
so if you plan to hide the giant revisionist admission basically and
基本上是修正主义者入场，并且已经看到了这一点，您将要
revisionist admission basically and already have seen this you're going to
already have seen this you're going to capture these dependencies between the
通过分解该活塞来捕获变量之间的这些依赖关系
capture these dependencies between the variables by factorizing this piston
variables by factorizing this piston vesicle distribution of Y as a market
作为市场的Y的囊泡分布，我将对其进行研究
vesicle distribution of Y as a market I'll go through it
I'll go through it okay this had potential trouble exits
好的，这可能会导致潜在的麻烦，然后我们当然会听到
okay this had potential trouble exits and then of course we are going to hear
and then of course we are going to hear these observations but I've defined
这些观察结果，但是我已经通过指令定义了
these observations but I've defined through a directive okay so very much to
through a directive okay so very much to emphasize that this is sort of an
强调这是一种有趣的新型图形，因为
emphasize that this is sort of an interesting new type of a graph because
interesting new type of a graph because obviously you're not going to capture
显然，您将不会使用有向图来捕获Y中的相关性
obviously you're not going to capture the correlations in Y with a directed
the correlations in Y with a directed graph because it makes no sense in the
图，因为它在正确的极限范围内没有意义，因此您将要捕获
graph because it makes no sense in the limits right so you're going to capture
limits right so you're going to capture them with an undirected graph but this
他们有一个无向图，但这真的你知道这是有向模型
them with an undirected graph but this really you know it is directed model as
really you know it is directed model as you see here Y is the parent of white is
您在这里看到Y是白色的父级，是X的父级，所以这是
you see here Y is the parent of white is the parent of X so this is the
the parent of X so this is the probability of observing XP assuming
假设图片为真实状态而观察XP的概率
probability of observing XP assuming that the true state of the picture
that the true state of the picture escaped if you actually want to avoid
如果您实际上想避免复杂的事情，请逃脱，您知道您可以做的是
escaped if you actually want to avoid complex this you know what you can do is
complex this you know what you can do is you can take this down here and lamp it
您可以将其放在此处并点灯，尝试连接电位，然后
you can take this down here and lamp it is try this connect potentials and then
is try this connect potentials and then actually work with an undirected graph
实际使用无向图，从不打扰并记住我们
actually work with an undirected graph and never bother with and remember we
and never bother with and remember we were doing this when we have this
当我们有足够的证据潜力时，我们会把它们混在一起
were doing this when we have this evidence potentials we will lumping them
evidence potentials we will lumping them on these terms all right so we can
就这些条款而言，这样我们就可以观看此问题以进行思考，这样您就可以避免
on these terms all right so we can watching this to think and so you avoid
watching this to think and so you avoid having to say that you have an
不得不说你有一个无向图，然后你知道
having to say that you have an undirected graph and then you know a
undirected graph and then you know a direct proportion of
直接比例
好的，所以当您留下混合物时，此图实际上在文献中
undirected graph and then you know a direct proportion of
all right so this graph actually in the literature when you have left a mixture
好的，所以当您留下混合物时，此图实际上在文献中
literature when you have left a mixture of on the left and the left is called
在左边和左边的那个叫做钱德拉（Chandra），我想我可能在某个地方
of on the left and the left is called the Chandra I think somewhere I may have
the Chandra I think somewhere I may have mentioned this in passing in in an
在较早的一次演讲中提到了这一点
mentioned this in passing in in an earlier lecture
earlier lecture demand is really the hidden Markov model
需求真的是隐藏的马尔可夫模型还可以，这是您遇到的问题
demand is really the hidden Markov model okay and it's such a problem as you
okay and it's such a problem as you observed markup on the field okay
在现场观察到的标记好吧，您观察得更快，因为您
observed markup on the field okay it's faster you observe because you
it's faster you observe because you don't know the rise but you know the
不知道上升，但您知道附加功能，所以影响是
don't know the rise but you know the extras all right so an influence is is a
extras all right so an influence is is a difficult problem so we need to discuss
困难的问题，所以我们需要讨论如何做到这一点
difficult problem so we need to discuss on how to do this okay
on how to do this okay this mention this right and maybe
这个提到这个权利，也许幻灯片中有两个例子
this mention this right and maybe there's an example of two in the slides
there's an example of two in the slides we take this model and your objective is
我们采用这种模型，您的目标是使用积分常数，因此
we take this model and your objective is the use of the integration constant so
the use of the integration constant so you know you give an X and you try to
您知道您给了X，然后尝试计算Y，所以它位于第一层
you know you give an X and you try to compute Y so this first layer it's in
compute Y so this first layer it's in that soil is basically this all right
基本上是土壤这是一个标记随机字段
that soil is basically this all right this is a markup random field it's very
this is a markup random field it's very popular on supervised problem is in an
在有监督的问题上很受欢迎的情况是在无监督的情况下可以正常工作
popular on supervised problem is in an unsupervised context this can work
unsupervised context this can work completely because for example you can
完全是因为，例如，您可以认为这种强调必须让您通过
completely because for example you can think this emphasis must nurses you pass
think this emphasis must nurses you pass from one picture to another but there
从一张图片到另一张图片，但有15张图片可以不连续
from one picture to another but there are 15 images you can have discontinuity
are 15 images you can have discontinuity somewhere from black to delight 70 right
从黑色到70左右的某个位置，所以在一个无人监督的问题中，此文件
somewhere from black to delight 70 right so in an unsupervised problem this file
so in an unsupervised problem this file will not work
不能正常工作，所以可以在这里使用它，或者
will not work all right so it's okay to use it here or
all right so it's okay to use it here or the supervised problem but it doesn't
有监督的问题，但不适用于有监督的问题
the supervised problem but it doesn't work for supervised problems
这些，所以让我就讨论这个高斯标记
these so let me just finish on this with discussing about this Gaussian mark of
discussing about this Gaussian mark of didn't specifically written intentional
没有专门为精确度指标而写的是众所周知的
didn't specifically written intentional from precision metrics is known for
from precision metrics is known for volumes Memphis's so again I have paper
卷孟菲斯的，所以我又在这里有纸笔，这句话
volumes Memphis's so again I have paper pencils here and the sentence
pencils here and the sentence pretentious if you like and you can
如果您喜欢，可以自命不凡，并且可以像这样或那样对它们进行参数化
pretentious if you like and you can parameterize them like this or like that
parameterize them like this or like that so immediately you can see if you
所以马上就可以看到私有化是否像这样
so immediately you can see if you privatization is given like this you
privatization is given like this you will get a decision basically but this
基本上会做出决定，但是这个高斯将要
will get a decision basically but this Gaussian is going to be on an
Gaussian is going to be on an information form because it's with in
信息表，因为它与Precision一起使用，这就是为什么我
information form because it's with in terms of Precision's and this why I
terms of Precision's and this why I delete all of them to mean all right and
删除所有这些都意味着没事，
该模型是根据精度矩阵编写的，尤其是
terms of Precision's and this why I delete all of them to mean all right and
this models were written in terms of precision matrices and particularly
该模型是根据精度矩阵编写的，尤其是
precision matrices and particularly because this precision met reserves past
因为过去已经满足了这个精度储备，所以我们的稀疏精度矩阵与
because this precision met reserves past we have sparse precision matrices versus
we have sparse precision matrices versus spots the various matrices can remember
发现各种矩阵可以记住我们在本课程中使用的方式
spots the various matrices can remember way that we used in this course a
way that we used in this course a Gaussian representation of a random
当我们传递给时，随机场的高斯表示
Gaussian representation of a random field when we had is passed to the
field when we had is passed to the audience methods and we did some where
受众群体的方法，我们做了一些应该问您构图的问题，而我
audience methods and we did some where it should ask you the composition and I
it should ask you the composition and I believe he did to see a formal like
相信他确实看过一本正规的书，也许是一本或两本
believe he did to see a formal like maybe homework one or two
我们去找你应该给你一个家庭作业的角落
we went to some kind of you should to give you a homework corner on the
give you a homework corner on the Gaussian random field it seems I know
高斯随机场似乎我肯定是正确的，但是正在发生的是
Gaussian random field it seems I know for sure right but what's happening is
for sure right but what's happening is metrics not the precision metrics and
指标而不是精度指标，尤其是跨指标不一样
metrics not the precision metrics and especially trans metrics is not the same
especially trans metrics is not the same as the space precision metrics okay
因为空间精度指标还可以，所以这个测量值
as the space precision metrics okay right so this this measurement around
right so this this measurement around the fields need to Espace precision
这些字段需要Espace精度指标，好吧，我们每个工作的数字
the fields need to Espace precision metrics okay the numbers we worked every
metrics okay the numbers we worked every into the course they were leading to
在课程中，它们又导致了稀疏协方差矩阵
into the course they were leading to sparse covariance matrix again you may
sparse covariance matrix again you may want to look on on on the notes so
想看笔记，所以很明显你根本不知道
want to look on on on the notes so obviously you don't even know the
obviously you don't even know the specialty of this lambda so here we use
这个lambda的特色，所以在这里我们使用成对铅笔
specialty of this lambda so here we use pairwise for pencils
pairwise for pencils so in essence in essence here if this
所以从本质上讲，如果此术语是数据，则在这里实现，如果
so in essence in essence here if this term is data or not it implements if
term is data or not it implements if there is link between two notes or not
在两个音符之间是否存在联系，因此本质上是学习
there is link between two notes or not so in essence learning the values of
so in essence learning the values of lambda is the same problem as learning a
lambda与学习图形模型的结构是相同的问题，所以
lambda is the same problem as learning a structure of the graphical model okay so
structure of the graphical model okay so you can pass this as an optimization
您可以将其作为优化问题通过，因为您可以学习
you can pass this as an optimization problem for you learn the structure of
problem for you learn the structure of the problem on the clock right
时钟正确的问题
所以我要给你一个扩展，我们对此进行了讨论，你知道你知道
problem for you learn the structure of the problem on the clock right
so I'm going to give you an extension we discussed on this you know you know
所以我要给你一个扩展，我们对此进行了讨论，你知道你知道
discussed on this you know you know Pat's model where the microphone that
帕特（Pat）的模型
Pat's model where the microphone that feels for y all right and and and then
feels for y all right and and and then we had an observation longer but can do
我们有更长的观察时间，但基本上可以做任何事情，可以是高斯或
we had an observation longer but can do anything basically can be a Gaussian or
anything basically can be a Gaussian or something like that so I mean I'm going
这样的事情，所以我的意思是我要给你一张照片，我要你
something like that so I mean I'm going to give you a picture and I want you to
to give you a picture and I want you to look at this picture and they'll be so
看看这张照片，他们会的，这样就没事了
look at this picture and they'll be so this is all right and things are
this is all right and things are basically
基本上是拉坦间隔的，所以我想让你告诉我
basically latane spaced so I want you to tell me
latane spaced so I want you to tell me what exactly you see when it comes to
当涉及到此链接的上下文时，您会看到什么
what exactly you see when it comes to the context of the links on this on the
the context of the links on this on the same as the change in time
与时间的变化相同，所以让我们在给定的时间说
same as the change in time okay so look let's say at a given time
okay so look let's say at a given time is the past
是过去
所以我们在这里看，这取决于谁-视图也取决于2-3对
okay so look let's say at a given time is the past
so we are looking here it depends on who - view but also depends on 2-3 right
看起来像这样，特别是给定的YT减去1 YT，YT的磁导率
looks like this alright the permeability of YT specifically given YT minus 1 YT
of YT specifically given YT minus 1 YT minus 2 and so this mattress is that you
减2，所以这个床垫是您在这里定义的稀疏度
minus 2 and so this mattress is that you see here define the sparsity of the
see here define the sparsity of the connections in time okay now now if you
现在可以及时连接到现在了，如果您注意到我将一遍又一遍地如此
connections in time okay now now if you notice I shall and again this is so
notice I shall and again this is so forth in one day but you can clean of
在一天之内，但您可以清洁这个身体，并保持良好状态
forth in one day but you can clean of this body was being on a good the
this body was being on a good the dependence at the given time between the
在给定时间Y变量之间的依赖性您如何看待
dependence at the given time between the Y variables what do you think how do you
Y variables what do you think how do you think they're being done if this was and
认为他们正在完成，如果培训视频的名称正确的话
think they're being done if this was and if the name of the training video right
if the name of the training video right and this were instances of the videos of
这是不同时间视频的实例，因此像素是
and this were instances of the videos of different times so the pixels are the
different times so the pixels are the given time the coordinator obviously in
给定时间，协调员显然可以及时看到情况如何
given time the coordinator obviously in time you can see all right how's it
time you can see all right how's it going to protonate the pixels to the
可以将像素质子化到给定的时间
going to protonate the pixels to the given time okay the sparsity the
given time okay the sparsity the evolution of wash in time
随着时间的流逝进化的过程好吗，这个Sigma是否取决于您的操作方式
evolution of wash in time okay this Sigma is it depend how you do
okay this Sigma is it depend how you do this around okay
好的，他们将定义振荡
this around okay they're going to define the oscillations
they're going to define the oscillations at the given time inspect okay
在给定的时间检查好吧，所以动力学的速度非常快
at the given time inspect okay so velocity in the dynamics but very
so velocity in the dynamics but very sparsely basically in capturing the
稀疏地基本上捕获了
sparsely basically in capturing the correlations in
correlations in for a given time alright so there is
在给定的时间里，所以有动态的概率图形
for a given time alright so there is this dynamic probabilistic graphical
this dynamic probabilistic graphical models actions very how the area of
可以很好地模拟动作，如果研究领域和杂乱无章的书籍
models actions very how the area of research and the disorganization book if
research and the disorganization book if anyone is interested to look it's a you
任何人都有兴趣看这是一个你知道它在宫殿，但我有一个
anyone is interested to look it's a you know it's in Palace but I have a
know it's in Palace but I have a complicated you know for review so if
复杂，您知道要进行审查，所以如果有人感兴趣，您可以让我知道
complicated you know for review so if anybody's interested you can let me know
anybody's interested you can let me know to make seven hundred pages of very new
制作七百页用于执行此类操作的非常新的算法
to make seven hundred pages of very new algorithms for doing this type of
algorithms for doing this type of problems but don't need this okay and
问题，但不需要这样做，我现在必须去滑动65，这样我们才能
problems but don't need this okay and I'd have to go now to slide 65 so we can
I'd have to go now to slide 65 so we can do maybe some of the training all right
做一些培训好吧好吧
do maybe some of the training all right all right
所以让我们至少回到这一点，我们可以开始与您讨论这个问题，因此我们写
so let's go back to this at least we can start to discuss you this so we write
start to discuss you this so we write this probability of y given theta if you
如果您还记得村庄的潜力，那么给定theta的y的概率就是
this probability of y given theta if you remember in village potentials is it to
remember in village potentials is it to the paper burns for some future
本文将为将来的某些功能而燃烧，直到
the paper burns for some future functions to the point of where the
functions to the point of where the clickstream so the type of distillations
点击流，因此具有最大似然估计和I的蒸馏类型
clickstream so the type of distillations with maximum likelihood estimation and I
with maximum likelihood estimation and I think once you know how to Emily to do
想一想，一旦您知道怎么做艾米莉（Emily），基本上就不会对地图进行估算
think once you know how to Emily to do basically a map estimation is nothing
basically a map estimation is nothing but to put the power out there and do
但要把功率放在那里并进行同样的计算，好吧，所以n
but to put the power out there and do the same sort of calculation okay so n
the same sort of calculation okay so n data points so this not my observations
数据点，所以这不是我的观察结果，我将这个功能强大
data points so this not my observations weii okay and i'm i put this powerful
weii okay and i'm i put this powerful man over in there because it's going to
在那里的人，因为它将简化我想做的计算
man over in there because it's going to simplify the calculations i want to do
看起来要反对这个，所以我们要带你去的人
looks like to show this against alright so we're gonna take the folks you're
so we're gonna take the folks you're gonna give a list notation function here
可以在这里给一个列表符号函数，然后指数将
gonna give a list notation function here all right and then the exponential will
all right and then the exponential will disappear if you can get the summation
如果可以得到总和然后将所有总和求和，则消失
disappear if you can get the summation of this and then summation over all the
of this and then summation over all the data point right the formulas equation
数据点对公式方程式的显示方式非常通用
data point right the formulas equation the way it is a very general it appears
the way it is a very general it appears in intimate settings in in machine
在机器学习的亲密环境中，但是这里困难的是
in intimate settings in in machine learning but here the difficult thing is
learning but here the difficult thing is you have there's no parameters and you
您没有参数，并且可以为各种语言设置语言
you have there's no parameters and you can envision language for your various
can envision language for your various parameters locally but unfortunately
本地参数，但是不幸的是，这次基本上是一团糟
parameters locally but unfortunately this time it's basically messes you are
this time it's basically messes you are because it released all of the
因为它释放了自此时间以来完成的所有参数
because it released all of the parameters since this time to complete
parameters since this time to complete this partition functions a
该分区的功能是您必须服务，就像我们所说的那样
this partition functions a you have to serve as we would say an
you have to serve as we would say an infinite problem you have to compute we
您必须计算的无限问题，我们必须基本上链接所有内容
infinite problem you have to compute we have to link basically everything
have to link basically everything together okay so this is not good
一起好吧，所以这不好，所以我们需要找到一些方法
together okay so this is not good all right so we need to find some way to
all right so we need to find some way to handle this problem okay so let's see
好好处理这个问题，让我们看看会导致什么
handle this problem okay so let's see what is going to lead into this
what is going to lead into this distribution form it looks like an
分布形式，它看起来像是指数函数类型
distribution form it looks like an exponential function type of
exponential function type of distribution so if we haven't proved it
分配，所以如果我们在本学期没有证明这一点，则在
distribution so if we haven't proved it on this semester it's in the notes from
on this semester it's in the notes from the Christmas semester so you can look
圣诞节学期，所以你基本上可以看一下
the Christmas semester so you can look at it basically the likelihood is a
at it basically the likelihood is a convex function of the parameters so it
参数的凸函数，因此它具有唯一的最大值，所以这是个好消息
convex function of the parameters so it has a unique maximum so that's good news
has a unique maximum so that's good news so this is a solution if we want to do
所以这是一个解决方案，如果我们要进行MLA，我的意思是这值得关注
so this is a solution if we want to do an MLA I mean this is of concern
an MLA I mean this is of concern obviously because if you have some
显然是因为如果您有一些分区功能，会发生什么
obviously because if you have some partition functions yes what happens
partition functions yes what happens right there's no I don't think that it
对，没有，我不认为它会给你一个凸函数，但是
right there's no I don't think that it will give you a convex function but
will give you a convex function but because of this exponential poly
由于这种指数多边形分布，您得到了一个凸函数
because of this exponential poly distributions you get a convex function
在参数上，有力地单击，然后单击，然后单击查看。
on the parameters the potentional click on click see so let's again when you
on click see so let's again when you take those who aspire to stay the same
带那些渴望保持原样的人
您可以将人功能简单地看到正确的视图，我认为这是错误的，我可以
on click see so let's again when you take those who aspire to stay the same
you get the person functions plain to see see right I think's wrong I okay
您可以将人功能简单地看到正确的视图，我认为这是错误的，我可以
see see right I think's wrong I okay alright so this is what you get and then
好吧，这就是你所得到的，然后从第二学期人类的手
alright so this is what you get and then from the second term human hand
from the second term human hand basically 2/3 relevance with respect to
基本上适合Z故事的2/3相关性，所以
basically 2/3 relevance with respect to fit the story of the of Z okay right so
fit the story of the of Z okay right so if you can exercise you can function
如果可以锻炼，就可以履行点击的承诺
if you can exercise you can function with respect to the promise of click see
with respect to the promise of click see it is nothing else but the expectation
除了人功能空间的期望之外，别无其他
it is nothing else but the expectation of the person function space see with
of the person function space see with respect to the underlying probability of
关于P的Y的潜在概率，这不是近似值或
respect to the underlying probability of P of Y this is no approximation or
P of Y this is no approximation or anything you know if you think you know
如果您认为知道分布是此路径的话，便会知道
anything you know if you think you know the distribution being the path of this
the distribution being the path of this potential to have nerves so you get
可能有神经，所以您可以总结出哪些茎和所有茎
potential to have nerves so you get summation which of the stems and all of
summation which of the stems and all of these things will actually give you the
这些东西实际上会为您提供参数theta C，所以事实上
these things will actually give you the parameters theta C so fact in the end of
parameters theta C so fact in the end of the day it is the expectation of the
这是对未来函数P的期望，请记住是这一天
the day it is the expectation of the future function P see remember is this
future function P see remember is this function PC that's affiliated with it as
与它关联的功能PC可以正常运行，因此您需要
function PC that's affiliated with it as T all right so you need expectation with
T all right so you need expectation with respect to the underlying distribution
对基础分布的了解表明您知道规模不存在
respect to the underlying distribution show you know the scale there's no
show you know the scale there's no evidence right dispose why i given theta
证据权处理我为什么给出theta，这是一个很好的计算权
evidence right dispose why i given theta and it's a beautiful calculation right
and it's a beautiful calculation right you have to you have to find this
你必须要找到这个期望并使它变得更糟
you have to you have to find this expectation and to make it worse you
expectation and to make it worse you have to find this expectation it's step
必须找到这个期望，这是梯度下降的一步，所以它是
have to find this expectation it's step in the gradient descent on good so it's
in the gradient descent on good so it's not like they're gonna be advanced and
不喜欢他们会进步，而您已经做了，因为这涉及到
not like they're gonna be advanced and you have done because this involves the
you have done because this involves the parameters theta and that's what we're
参数theta，这就是我们感兴趣的具体内容，因此您将
parameters theta and that's what we're interested concrete so you're going to
interested concrete so you're going to have to do iterations for that okay so
要做迭代就可以了，所以让我们来看一些极端的事情
have to do iterations for that okay so let's see something extremely
let's see something extremely interesting that comes out of this okay
有趣的事就可以了，所以如果您通过我，这就是
interesting that comes out of this okay so if you passed me that this is the
so if you passed me that this is the expectation of the treacherous functions
对流程中一步一步看到的奸诈功能的期望
expectation of the treacherous functions we see with a step to the flow
we see with a step to the flow distribution P of Y right surviving this
Y分布P幸存于这种期望注解和第一个
distribution P of Y right surviving this anotation of expectation and the first
anotation of expectation and the first term all right okay hopefully I don't
学期好吧，希望我不认为我错过了你的排名之一
term all right okay hopefully I don't think I have missed it one of rank you
think I have missed it one of rank you so I don't know if they won over them
所以我不知道他们是否赢了他们消失了，好吧，这是
so I don't know if they won over them disappeared there okay and this is
disappeared there okay and this is outside the parentheses or you guys
括号之外，或者你们对我来说是第二位，所以这是N分之一
outside the parentheses or you guys second for me so this is one over N
second for me so this is one over N times the summation of the future
乘以未来函数的总和PC计算固定比率
times the summation of the future functions PC compute the fixed rate the
functions PC compute the fixed rate the for y I so this is what you get from the
对于y，所以这就是您从第一步中得到的内容，所以请看一下并告诉我
for y I so this is what you get from the first step so look at this and tell me
first step so look at this and tell me in a more compact notation what is that
用更紧凑的表示是什么
这么多的结束时间，所以您有一个数据集端点，
first step so look at this and tell me in a more compact notation what is that
so many of the end times so you have a data set endpoints and you
这么多的结束时间，所以您有一个数据集端点，
so you have a data set endpoints and you compute this crucial function C of all
计算所有数据端口的关键功能C，那么它是一个
compute this crucial function C of all the data ports so what is that it is an
the data ports so what is that it is an expectation of this chain right with
该链权对投资网络发行的期望
expectation of this chain right with respect investment web distribution
不
nope
我们的样本会从这个分布中杀死她
our samples they'll kill her from this distribution
they'll kill her from this distribution so when I ran the samples the
因此，当我运行样本时，分布的近似值为
so when I ran the samples the approximation of distribution having a
approximation of distribution having a corner distribution with other functions
与其他功能的角落分布不是相机类型的东西
corner distribution with other functions it's not the camera type thing
你知道关于经验分布的期望，所以基本上
you know expectation with respect to the empirical distribution okay so basically
empirical distribution okay so basically the dissonant with respect to the
关于参数的不谐调是期望
the dissonant with respect to the parameters to the say is the expectation
parameters to the say is the expectation of this XI with respect to the empirical
关于经验分布的XI的期望
of this XI with respect to the empirical distribution - the expectation of
distribution - the expectation of receiver respect to the exact
接收者尊重确切的分布，所以基本上，如果您设置
receiver respect to the exact distribution so basically if you set
distribution so basically if you set this you say in this case you set this
这个你说在这种情况下，你将这个设置为零，基本上我们有一个
this you say in this case you set this equal to zero and basically we have a
equal to zero and basically we have a problem that we were discussing in the
我们在最近三，四堂课中讨论的问题，以及
problem that we were discussing in the last three or four lectures and that
last three or four lectures and that problem is not it's made no marching you
问题是，它没有前进，所以您看到了每个人的期望
problem is not it's made no marching you see that so expectations of each
see that so expectations of each respective functions for each case needs
每种情况下各自的功能需要太多
respective functions for each case needs too much
too much that was funny expectations under the
在经验分布下这是一个有趣的期望，有些请走开
that was funny expectations under the empirical distribution some please away
empirical distribution some please away to implement actually rest okay so
实施实际上可以休息，所以您必须将其设置为等于
to implement actually rest okay so actively you have to set this equal to
actively you have to set this equal to this moment
这是根据经验确定的时刻
this moment defined for the under the empirical
defined for the under the empirical distribution okay
分布还可以
您可以说我们称迷宫为真正的迷宫，所以我们找不到它
defined for the under the empirical distribution okay
you can say that we call the maze that actually we so it's not going to find
您可以说我们称迷宫为真正的迷宫，所以我们找不到它
actually we so it's not going to find the pinnacle distribution of okay okay
顶峰分布好吧好吧，您将需要整合盖茨圣经
the pinnacle distribution of okay okay you will need to integrate gates Bibles
在概念上看起来非常相似，并且自动就像计算
looks very similar conceptually and automatically like computing the
automatically like computing the partition function will be integrated in
分区函数将有效地集成到Y中，您将获得
partition function will be integrated in Y so effectively this terms that you get
Y so effectively this terms that you get the look like partition functions
看起来分区函数完成的位置并不是任意的
the look like partition functions completed not arbitrary where they are
completed not arbitrary where they are integrating over Y takes an integrating
在Y上积分需要积分知识，但它们仍然是分区的
integrating over Y takes an integrating knowledge but they are still partition
knowledge but they are still partition functions and I'm going to give you the
函数，我将给您答案，然后我们将在
functions and I'm going to give you the answer and then we'll come back to it at
answer and then we'll come back to it at the end of the day so the answer comes
一天结束，所以答案来了
基本上说，参数theta C的状态的建立是有一个
answer and then we'll come back to it at the end of the day so the answer comes
basically that the building of the state of the parameters theta C is there is a
基本上说，参数theta C的状态的建立是有一个
of the parameters theta C is there is a summation in the hidden value
隐藏价值的总和将那些整合出来，基本上就是
summation in the hidden value integrate those out and basically is the
integrate those out and basically is the difference of two expectations one of
两个期望的差异之一是期望的分布
difference of two expectations one of them is the distribution of expectation
them is the distribution of expectation a beta distribution of Y and the other
Y的beta分布，而另一个实际上是实际时刻，因此
a beta distribution of Y and the other one is actually the actual moment so
one is actually the actual moment so this moment marching here with its
此时此刻，它在其中之一中集成了功能，行进到了这里
this moment marching here with its integrated out okay in one of the
integrated out okay in one of the moments Y is basically integrated out in
基本上，Y的瞬间集成到另一个中，Y固定的瞬间
moments Y is basically integrated out in the other a moment Y is fixed
the other a moment Y is fixed okay Y space and this has a magical
好的，Y空间，并且基于
okay Y space and this has a magical total firm implementations based on
total firm implementations based on expectation maximization actually what
期望最大化实际上与通用名称有什么关系
expectation maximization actually what is great with the name generalized
is great with the name generalized expectation maximization so we don't
期望最大化，所以我们不必在周四浪费一些时间，然后
expectation maximization so we don't have to waste some on Thursday and then
have to waste some on Thursday and then we will give the stability and
我们将为此给出近似的稳定性和异议性
we will give the stability and dissentient of approximation for this
dissentient of approximation for this type of problems
问题类型